I won't cry.
I can't be the one crying...
I'm the older one...
I gotta keep it together.
Looks like you're doing a bit better, Saaya.
Sorry, Senpai. I'm fine now.
Tokyo Metropolitan Police Hospital Front Entrance Station
Today's area is Nakano Ward...
Yup. Good thing it's not far from here.
We'll be sticking together today
so it's not as scary!
Let's get our revenge
and find those postboxes!
Yeah!
Nakano Ward
Suginami Ward
A blue postbox!
Kaido Senpai?
Thank you.
Ugh... I can't see!
It's probably too late
to submit something now...
Finally! A postbox!
A guy? How are you alive?
Oh, well. It's not like there's cops anymore.
All I have to do is kill you
and submit my entry!
Who are you?! You gonna attack me?!
Who cares? Just ignore him.
I'm Rika Suzuki.
Of course, I'm attacking you.
Wait, why did I just—
I reject!
What? You "reject"?! Whatever!
I'm gonna kill you! And make it out alive!
I missed?!
Damn you, kid!
What do I do with this?
If I use it now, then...
Like worrying will do me any good!
Damn it!
See ya! Hope you stay alive, Suzuki-san!
Tasers really come in handy
in times like this.
Weapons aren't about specs.
It's how you use them.
Maybe you'll learn that later tonight.
First entry: no Prime Right.
Second entry: with Prime Right.
Five minutes from starting point
and ten minutes from execution point...
Oh, that reminds me.
Now... Oh my, look at you. How unlucky.
You must have cut an artery when you fell.
Maybe you shouldn't use
steel pipes like that.
You're the one who shot me!
At this rate, you'll die. What to do?
You bitch!
Don't you want to live? I know how.
I'm so sick of this!
I bet these postboxes don't even exist!
There's no way we can beat the Emperor!
Everyone's destined to die!
Eren Senpai...
I can't do this anymore!
I wanna go to my parents'...
We're so helpless.
We can't even find a postbox.
Sorry, Saneatsu...
It's time. We will now
begin tallying the majority.
As a result of Tasuketsu, I'm...
- Alive or Dead
We've passed midnight.
Could that mean...
Saneatsu! You really came back to life!
Huh? Back to life?
Saaya?
I'm so weak.
I was about to break our promise...
but I'm okay now.
I remembered that I have nothing to be
scared about as long as I have our promise.
Saaya...
When did the two of them get so close?!
Senpai! I was dead, too! Hold me!
Go die again!
We were all dead and then
brought back to life?
Look! The lights!
Everyone who died from Tasuketsu was revived!
W-Why?! Why would they come back to life?!
I could have gotten rid of men
once and for all!
I came all this way just
to see their dead bodies!
Too bad I'm the only one here.
Men are always this way...
Just like my dad!
Just like the guys in class!
All men are nothing but power-hungry trash!
Even smart ones like you! Even now!
It's proof that I'm right!
Go to hell!
So Mika Kaido isn't the Emperor...
Then that means...
Is there no announcement
on the next designated area tonight?
So the revival did work... Mido, Iruga.
Thanks for the trouble, Isshiki.
Just like you said, Mido.
There was a male who was alive.
Short hair with an accent... in
grade school or middle school.
I figured...
Owner of the quasi-major
Prime Right to Rejection!
But he doesn't seem very bright.
He used his best idea this early in the game.
Isshiki, bring around the car.
Roger that.
Iruga, do you recognize the kid she mentioned?
Nah. Nope, sorry.
You heard the lady.
Grade school or middle school.
Fine. I guess it can wait.
Besides, how rude of Isshiki...
Calling Tasuketsu a "game".
She must be thinking
the Emperor's just playing.
Now...
The fun's about to start...
W-Why?!
You are currently looking at this
screen in Tokyo Prefecture.
Why is there another question?!
No... Then everyone who came back to life...
Could it be a Prime Right?!
Shoot, they got me! This is
the Prime Right to Re-execution!
It was all someone's plan...
and they used my question?
They must have done it to prevent
revival of victims later on.
What are you kids yelling about
so late at night?!
Look at the screen! Please, hurry!
The screen?
You are currently looking at this
screen in Tokyo Prefecture.
We've passed 12:10AM.
H-How?
He was looking at the screen...
Idiots will just get in the way.
The Emperor's motive isn't
to play a game, it's "recovery".
I don't need imbeciles who can't
understand something as simple as that.
Say goodbye to hope...
Finally, it begins.
You are currently looking at this
screen in Tokyo Prefecture.
Prime Rights: 13 left
Rights: 47 left
Today's Area
Nerima Ward
2,215,466 people left
The Tasuketsu from two days ago...
All the males died from that, right?
How were we brought back to life?
Yesterday's question...
"As a result of Tasuketsu,
I'm 'alive' or 'dead'".
A deficit of the dead?
As the majority, the dead were
made "undead"... meaning alive?
Are the dead part of Tasuketsu? Can't be...
Besides, how could dead people
come back to life?
If you're gonna say that, how can people
die from a simple tally in the first place?
It's my fault. If I hadn't used
that question so soon...
Omi, what's wrong?
Narita-kun...
Call me Saneatsu.
We're in this together now, aren't we?
We're friends. No need to be formal.
Friends?
S-Saneatsu...
Yeah, there we go!
Hey, Sensei?
Were you the informatics teacher
for all the first-years?
Yeah, why?
Then can you tell me what kind
of students those kids are?
Sure, if you tell me more about you.
I'm not too familiar since it's my first year.
Sure, we're a team now.
Fujishiro, Saaya
Fujishiro is from Class D.
Good grades, never in trouble.
An excellent student all around.
She's even part of the Student Council.
Fujishiro, Saaya
Narita, Saneatsu
Narita is from Class A. Not the best
at studying, but he's pretty sharp.
Narita, Saneatsu
Sato, Kazuhiko
Sato's also from Class A.
He's always loud in class, but
he can make friends with anyone.
Sato, Kazuhiko
Jin, Omi
Jin is from Class C. He usually
sits quietly alone in class.
So?
I don't know what he was down about,
but he did smile for the first time.
You're a nice guy, Saneatsu.
It's not like that. I just...
When I was four, my mom and I were out
when a truck came and...
Somehow, I survived.
But by the time I woke up,
my amazing mom was gone from this world.
My dad's always overseas for work,
and I shut myself in my room.
I was starting to think
I'd be better off dead when...
Hey! I just moved in next door.
I'm Ryuta Ichinose!
Are you Narita-san?
Nice to meet you!
From then on, it didn't matter
if I agreed or what time it was.
He always came barging in out of nowhere.
But I found myself going along
with Ryuta's antics... and enjoying it.
Hey, Ryuta... Why did you come talk to me?
Did you know? There's something
real precious in this world!
What's that?
Parents, siblings, loved ones,
and best friends!
Now I have more of them!
Since we're best friends!
I've made it my goal since then... to
help someone like Ryuta saved me.
I wanna be a person who can save others.
That's why helping someone
is actually for my own merit.
I'm not some noble person.
Starting today, let's meet three times
each day in the afternoon, evening,
and at night to share information more often.
It'll help us expand our search
and improve efficiency.
If only there was another
hint besides postboxes...
I'm about to ask you a question.
Answer with "yes" or "no".
Can you promise not to run or resist?
Y-Yes. I promise.
I have something to tell you.
I prefer speaking to Saaya Fujishiro,
but it can't be helped.
Let's go somewhere else.
I've killed Mika Kaido.
I'll let you ask one question
based on that information.
Don't say anything else.
Why do you rely so much on guns, Senpai?
How did you arrive at that question?
I just assumed you killed her with a gun...
but there's only so many bullets you can use.
And you don't seem to have any
reservations about using them.
You came up and actually spoke to me.
I assume that was to test
if I'm worth talking to.
That goes to show how
important your matter is...
Fair enough.
In fact, I'm glad you were the one
I ran into, Saneatsu Narita.
To be clear, Mika Kaido was the one who
killed us with the "male or female" question.
She was screaming about some nonsense,
but she was too dangerous
to be roaming free, so I shot her.
Kaido Senpai...
Before I tell you, I want to be sure.
Has the number of people
in your group changed?
No.
Has anyone changed in their appearance?
Finally, who suggested running away
from school that day?
I think it was...
Get in!
Sensei!
I see, that makes sense.
I suppose I was wrong...
but I was also right.
At first, I presumed that
Omi Jin was the Emperor.
Omi?!
On the first day of Tasuketsu,
I didn't just acquire a gun.
I acquired something else.
Prime Right
The Prime Right of Obtainment.
A Prime Right!
Precisely because I gained this strange
power, I became suspicious of Omi Jin.
Are you gonna shoot me?!
Of course I am.
I reject.
I found myself responding to a question
I had no intention of answering.
And the bullet I shot at point-blank
range missed him completely.
"I reject".
His right must be something
along the lines of "Rejection".
Right of Rejection
As for forcing response of a question,
I suspect it's a right to "Response
Enforcement" or something like that.
Right of Response Enforcement
Judging from the power balance of the two
abilities, Rejection must be a Prime Right,
Prime Right
and Response Enforcement must be a Right...
Right
Although their names aren't exact.
Omi?
I suspect he had a Prime Right and Right
before Tasuketsu even began.
B-But he's not the Emperor, is he?
That's not even the main concern.
Huh?
There's a traitor among your group.
A traitor?!
Who knows their motive, but
there's damage already being done.
They likely possess a Prime Right.
You already know who it is?
I'm fairly sure.
Sudo Senpai, do you want
to rejoin the group?!
I know you may have killed someone, but...
You were only acting rationally
so you could beat the Emperor...
I think we need you!
Thank you. A part of me
is saved by your words.
I'll answer a question in return.
Is there anything you want to ask?
I guess... about your Prime Right and
your theory on the revival last night?
I don't know about Rights,
but Prime Rights will demand you take
a risk when opening the envelope.
Prime Right
The risk involves... loss of a body part.
What?! Then—
I chose the scrotum.
There's no need for reproductive
functions in this situation,
and it's best to get rid of any vital points.
The Prime Right I gained is... Obtainment.
Right of Obtainment
Once I obtain a certain object,
I can maintain its number
and guarantee its availability.
So your supply of bullets is...
Unlimited, of course.
Why do you rely so much on guns, Senpai?
So that's why...
As for the revival of the dead,
how do you make sense of it?
Well, our theory is that "absence
of the dead" meant "undead"
which brought them back to life...
But I think the condition of the deaths
being "as a result of Tasuketsu"
was the main key.
It turned death on its head
by forcefully replacing the prerequisite
of directing questions
only towards survivors.
You mean the person who
wrote the question knew?
Who knows? But I believe they
submitted it with good intentions.
Perhaps they truly just
wanted to revive the victims.
You are currently looking at this
screen in Tokyo Prefecture.
The same can't be said
for the second question.
I first assumed it was a plan devised
by the Emperor, in response to the revival.
But if they were to intervene like that,
why not just kill people on their own?
It's reasonable to conclude
that someone used their Prime Right
or Right to enforce a second question.
Someone else...
If it's a matter of sabotaging
the revival method,
the most effective question is
"You were just revived; Yes or No".
But if the revival doesn't work, the question
would be directed towards survivors.
This results in a unanimous "no". Game over.
The second question was likely submitted
by someone who couldn't determine
the results of the first question.
And to top it off, the Emperor's explanation
of the rules doesn't fit the reality.
The majority side
of the two answers will die.
If they wanted to hide the revival method,
why not just create a scheme
that doesn't allow for them,
or nullify those submissions?
But they didn't do either.
This shows that the Emperor doesn't
have a good grasp of Tasuketsu.
If that's the case for the Emperor,
it's unlikely that the questioner recognized
the loopholes behind the revival method.
Either they randomly came up with it,
or they analyzed the situation like me
and found an answer...
What is it?
Nothing, I'm just in awe...
Let's cut to the chase.
Be careful around Saaya Fujishiro.
Tasuketsu may be important, but the top
priority right now is eliminating the traitor.
Once it's too late, even submitting
questions will be dangerous.
Saaya...
I'm about to tell you everything
I've unraveled so far.
Listen carefully and use it
to your advantage.
Senpai, thank y—
I chose the path to use force
against the Emperor.
I don't want to drag you all
into something so dangerous.
About our talk...
I understand everything.
I'll become your sword
and defeat the Emperor.
In the meantime, go find postboxes
so you can continue surviving.
For sure!
What are you going to do
when you meet up with the group?
I have a plan. My strategy
and what to do next...
Is that so? I have faith in you.
Good Intentions
Good luck.